[
    {
        "story_idx": 0,
        "question": "Aetherium Tides: In what year did the Navigator first pierce the Maelstrom?",
        "answer": "872 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 1,
        "question": "Aetherium Tides: What was the Maelstrom of Azure?",
        "answer": "Churning vortex"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 2,
        "question": "Aetherium Tides: What was the name of the skyship that was lost under Captain Corvus?",
        "answer": "Star Wanderer"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 3,
        "question": "Aetherium Tides: What was the name of the Navigator's vessel?",
        "answer": "Silver Heron"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 4,
        "question": "Aetherium Tides: What was the name of the device equipped on the vessel?",
        "answer": "Aetherium Nullifier"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 5,
        "question": "Aetherium Tides: Where was the artificer who designed the device from?",
        "answer": "Crystal Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 6,
        "question": "Aetherium Tides: What artifact was the voyage undertaken to retrieve?",
        "answer": "Codex of the Sunken City"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 7,
        "question": "Aetherium Tides: What epic poem chronicled the daring voyage?",
        "answer": "The Aetherium Queen"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 8,
        "question": "The Chronoplast Defection: What was the date of the 23rd Cycle of the Great Purification?",
        "answer": "2147 A.D."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 9,
        "question": "The Chronoplast Defection: Where was the Chronoplast Chamber located?",
        "answer": "Beneath London"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 10,
        "question": "The Chronoplast Defection: What is the official designation of the former city of London?",
        "answer": "Sector 7"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 11,
        "question": "The Chronoplast Defection: What year was the formation of the Concord of Appalachia?",
        "answer": "Around 2150 A.D."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 12,
        "question": "The Chronoplast Defection: What was the name of the restricted temporal strata files?",
        "answer": "Project Chimera"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 13,
        "question": "The Chronoplast Defection: What was the ultimate goal detailed in the Project Chimera files?",
        "answer": "Genetic rewrite"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 14,
        "question": "The Chronoplast Defection: What protocol was defied by the Temporal Leap?",
        "answer": "Chronoplast Protocol"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 15,
        "question": "The Chronoplast Defection: What article was defied by the Temporal Leap?",
        "answer": "Article VI"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 16,
        "question": "Wyrmwood Crown: In what year did the king of Aethelgard die?",
        "answer": "1348"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 17,
        "question": "Wyrmwood Crown: In which realm did the king die?",
        "answer": "Aethelgard"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 18,
        "question": "Wyrmwood Crown: Where did the king of Aethelgard die?",
        "answer": "Grove of Whispers"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 19,
        "question": "Wyrmwood Crown: What was the name of the war that began after the king's assassination?",
        "answer": "Wyrmwood Crown War"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 20,
        "question": "Wyrmwood Crown: What kind of trees were important in the story?",
        "answer": "Wyrmwood"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 21,
        "question": "Wyrmwood Crown: What held the essence of Aethelgard's ancestral spirits?",
        "answer": "Wyrmwood trees"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 22,
        "question": "Wyrmwood Crown: What did the insurgent armies want to control?",
        "answer": "Magical timber"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 23,
        "question": "Wyrmwood Crown: Who was widely attributed with the king's assassination?",
        "answer": "Lord Malachi"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 24,
        "question": "Voidheart Symphony: What year did the 'Whispers of the Outer Dark' occur?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 25,
        "question": "Voidheart Symphony: Which probe detected the anomaly?",
        "answer": "*Odyssey VI*"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 26,
        "question": "Voidheart Symphony: Near which dwarf planet was the initial data dismissed?",
        "answer": "Sedna"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 27,
        "question": "Voidheart Symphony: On what Stardate were the sonic patterns analyzed?",
        "answer": "7345.1"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 28,
        "question": "Voidheart Symphony: Where was the Global Space Agency's hub located?",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 29,
        "question": "Voidheart Symphony: Over which city were inexplicable aurora displays seen?",
        "answer": "Novosibirsk"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 30,
        "question": "Voidheart Symphony: In which desert were temporal distortions witnessed?",
        "answer": "Gobi"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 31,
        "question": "Voidheart Symphony: Near what location was the fortified research station?",
        "answer": "Luna City"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 32,
        "question": "Iron Bloom Uprising: What event marked a turning point for the Cogsmiths in 1876?",
        "answer": "Great Ignition"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 33,
        "question": "Iron Bloom Uprising: In what year did the Great Ignition occur?",
        "answer": "1876"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 34,
        "question": "Iron Bloom Uprising: Where did the Great Ignition take place?",
        "answer": "Aethelburg"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 35,
        "question": "Iron Bloom Uprising: Which manufacturing district was involved in clandestine meetings?",
        "answer": "Gearsburg"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 36,
        "question": "Iron Bloom Uprising: What date were initial demands presented?",
        "answer": "May 14, 1876"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 37,
        "question": "Iron Bloom Uprising: What year were the initial demands presented?",
        "answer": "1876"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 38,
        "question": "Iron Bloom Uprising: What organization presented the initial demands?",
        "answer": "Mechanical League"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 39,
        "question": "Iron Bloom Uprising: What uprising was ignited by the rejection of demands?",
        "answer": "Iron Bloom"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 40,
        "question": "The Serpent's Atlas: When did a discovery occur within the Royal Geographical Society of London?",
        "answer": "Summer of 1798"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 41,
        "question": "The Serpent's Atlas: In what city was the Royal Geographical Society located?",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 42,
        "question": "The Serpent's Atlas: What location had meticulously drawn coastlines mentioned in comparison?",
        "answer": "The New World"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 43,
        "question": "The Serpent's Atlas: What year did Captain Cook explore the Pacific territories?",
        "answer": "In 1770"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 44,
        "question": "The Serpent's Atlas: Which company charted trade routes to the Indies in 1602?",
        "answer": "Dutch East India Company"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 45,
        "question": "The Serpent's Atlas: What year did the Dutch East India Company chart routes to the Indies?",
        "answer": "In 1602"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 46,
        "question": "The Serpent's Atlas: What was the title of the peculiar charts found?",
        "answer": "The Serpent's Atlas"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 47,
        "question": "The Serpent's Atlas: Near what place did a drowning tragedy occur in 1795?",
        "answer": "Near Weymouth"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 48,
        "question": "Sunken Star Prophecy: What year did the submersible descend into the Mariana Trench?",
        "answer": "2077"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 49,
        "question": "Sunken Star Prophecy: What was the name of the submersible?",
        "answer": "Triton's Eye"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 50,
        "question": "Sunken Star Prophecy: What was the target site in the Mariana Trench?",
        "answer": "Lost City of Aethelgard"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 51,
        "question": "Sunken Star Prophecy: What painted the outlines of colossal structures?",
        "answer": "sonar"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 52,
        "question": "Sunken Star Prophecy: What was found amongst the cyclopean ruins?",
        "answer": "Prophecy Chamber"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 53,
        "question": "Sunken Star Prophecy: What foretold Aethelgard's demise?",
        "answer": "Sunken Star"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 54,
        "question": "Sunken Star Prophecy: What was woven into the city's foundations?",
        "answer": "energy conduits"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 55,
        "question": "Sunken Star Prophecy: What impactor reshaped Earth?",
        "answer": "Chicxulub"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 56,
        "question": "The Geist Market: What year did the Blackwood Manor tragedy occur?",
        "answer": "1866"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 57,
        "question": "The Geist Market: In what year was the Geist Market active?",
        "answer": "1878"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 58,
        "question": "The Geist Market: Where did the \"Night of the Crimson Ribbon\" happen?",
        "answer": "Vienna"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 59,
        "question": "The Geist Market: What year was the \"Night of the Crimson Ribbon\"?",
        "answer": "1942"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 60,
        "question": "The Geist Market: Where was the Geist Market located?",
        "answer": "Saint Jude's Cathedral"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 61,
        "question": "The Geist Market: What kind of treaties were bartered at the market?",
        "answer": "forgotten"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 62,
        "question": "The Geist Market: What kind of energy filled the air?",
        "answer": "residual"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 63,
        "question": "Quantum Weavers: What year did the rupture occur?",
        "answer": "1776"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 64,
        "question": "Quantum Weavers: What was the name of the Timeless City?",
        "answer": "Aethelburg"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 65,
        "question": "Quantum Weavers: Where was the origin of the rupture suspected to be?",
        "answer": "Terra"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 66,
        "question": "Quantum Weavers: What were the beings dispatched to mend the realities called?",
        "answer": "Chronos-Weavers"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 67,
        "question": "Quantum Weavers: What is the name of the Loom within Aethelburg?",
        "answer": "Loom of Ages"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 68,
        "question": "Quantum Weavers: What was the suspected experiment's name?",
        "answer": "Philadelphia Experiment"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 69,
        "question": "Quantum Weavers: What did the Chronos-Keepers notice in 1776?",
        "answer": "grave rupture"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 70,
        "question": "Quantum Weavers: What was the result of the experiment?",
        "answer": "rupture"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 71,
        "question": "Crimson Ash Legacy: What year is mentioned in the story?",
        "answer": "Year 742"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 72,
        "question": "Crimson Ash Legacy: What lands are described?",
        "answer": "Ashfall"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 73,
        "question": "Crimson Ash Legacy: Where was the legendary blade forged?",
        "answer": "Scarred Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 74,
        "question": "Crimson Ash Legacy: What battle is mentioned?",
        "answer": "Blackwood Pass"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 75,
        "question": "Crimson Ash Legacy: What is the name of the legendary blade?",
        "answer": "Crimson Ash"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 76,
        "question": "Crimson Ash Legacy: What does the cursed weapon consume?",
        "answer": "The essence"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 77,
        "question": "Crimson Ash Legacy: What clan is mentioned?",
        "answer": "Ashwood Clan"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 78,
        "question": "Crimson Ash Legacy: What kind of destiny is the clan known for facing?",
        "answer": "Grim destiny"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 79,
        "question": "Geodecity Blues: What was the name of the city?",
        "answer": "Geodecity"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 80,
        "question": "Geodecity Blues: What was the energy core called?",
        "answer": "Pulsing Heart"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 81,
        "question": "Geodecity Blues: Which sector was opulent?",
        "answer": "Radiance Sector"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 82,
        "question": "Geodecity Blues: What year was mentioned for the Radiance Sector?",
        "answer": "2407 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 83,
        "question": "Geodecity Blues: What were the lower tiers called?",
        "answer": "Shardlands"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 84,
        "question": "Geodecity Blues: What were the dim crystalline caves called?",
        "answer": "Deep Crystalline Caves"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 85,
        "question": "Geodecity Blues: What was the name of the desperate gamble?",
        "answer": "Coreward Push"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 86,
        "question": "Geodecity Blues: When was the Coreward Push initiated?",
        "answer": "17th day"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 87,
        "question": "The Whispering Mire: What year did the events in the Blackwood Bayou take place?",
        "answer": "1788"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 88,
        "question": "The Whispering Mire: Where is the Blackwood Bayou located?",
        "answer": "Near Fort St. Augustine"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 89,
        "question": "The Whispering Mire: What is the local name for the region the patrol entered?",
        "answer": "Whispering Mire"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 90,
        "question": "The Whispering Mire: When did the Siege of Charleston occur?",
        "answer": "Three years prior"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 91,
        "question": "The Whispering Mire: During which battle did the Sergeant's brother fall?",
        "answer": "Battle of Quebec"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 92,
        "question": "The Whispering Mire: When did the Battle of Quebec take place?",
        "answer": "1759"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 93,
        "question": "The Whispering Mire: Where was one of the young recruits from?",
        "answer": "Savannah"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 94,
        "question": "The Whispering Mire: Where was the other young recruit from?",
        "answer": "The Carolinas"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 95,
        "question": "Cipher Lords of Mars: When did the groundbreaking discovery occur?",
        "answer": "Spring of 2242"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 96,
        "question": "Cipher Lords of Mars: Where was the groundbreaking discovery made?",
        "answer": "Valles Marineris"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 97,
        "question": "Cipher Lords of Mars: What were the unearthed items initially cataloged as?",
        "answer": "Sol 4 Relics"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 98,
        "question": "Cipher Lords of Mars: Where were the unearthed items initially stored?",
        "answer": "New Elysium Repository"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 99,
        "question": "Cipher Lords of Mars: What season was it on Mars during the discovery?",
        "answer": "Red Dust Season"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 100,
        "question": "Cipher Lords of Mars: What were the unearthed artifacts described as?",
        "answer": "Peculiar metallic"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 101,
        "question": "Cipher Lords of Mars: What were the unearthed artifacts truly?",
        "answer": "Sophisticated data keys"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 102,
        "question": "Cipher Lords of Mars: Where was the painstaking analysis performed?",
        "answer": "Olympus Mons laboratory"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 103,
        "question": "Steel Seraphim Down: What year did the Steel Seraphim meet her end?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 104,
        "question": "Steel Seraphim Down: What city was the Steel Seraphim above?",
        "answer": "Last Bastion City"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 105,
        "question": "Steel Seraphim Down: Where were the Steel Seraphim's wings forged?",
        "answer": "Sky-Forges"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 106,
        "question": "Steel Seraphim Down: What era was heralded by the silence?",
        "answer": "vulnerable era"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 107,
        "question": "Steel Seraphim Down: What tower was visible during the fall?",
        "answer": "Chronos Tower"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 108,
        "question": "Steel Seraphim Down: What plains were mentioned in the story?",
        "answer": "Whispering Plains"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 109,
        "question": "Steel Seraphim Down: What celestial event occurred?",
        "answer": "Solstice"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 110,
        "question": "Steel Seraphim Down: What was encroaching on the city?",
        "answer": "Gloom"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 111,
        "question": "Dream Rot Plague: In what year did the Dream Rot Plague reach Bristol?",
        "answer": "1348"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 112,
        "question": "Dream Rot Plague: What port city did the plague first reach?",
        "answer": "Bristol"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 113,
        "question": "Dream Rot Plague: What king reigned when the plague reached Bristol?",
        "answer": "Edward III"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 114,
        "question": "Dream Rot Plague: Where were afflicted individuals found muttering?",
        "answer": "St. Nicholas Market"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 115,
        "question": "Dream Rot Plague: What ethereal things manifested from sleeping victims?",
        "answer": "decaying lilies"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 116,
        "question": "Dream Rot Plague: What kind of shadows manifested around the afflicted?",
        "answer": "putrid shadows"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 117,
        "question": "Dream Rot Plague: What Abbey did the scribe Brother Silas belong to?",
        "answer": "St. Augustine"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 118,
        "question": "Dream Rot Plague: Who commissioned the documentation of the bizarre phenomena?",
        "answer": "Bishop Geoffrey"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 119,
        "question": "The Nomad Stitch: When did the Great Sundering occur?",
        "answer": "843 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 120,
        "question": "The Nomad Stitch: How often did the Remembrance Weave happen?",
        "answer": "Every five cycles"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 121,
        "question": "The Nomad Stitch: What was the name of the Hide-Beast carrying Aethel?",
        "answer": "Greatheart"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 122,
        "question": "The Nomad Stitch: Where did the journey in 912 AE go?",
        "answer": "Sunstone Plains"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 123,
        "question": "The Nomad Stitch: Which beast was used for the 912 AE journey?",
        "answer": "Earthshaker"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 124,
        "question": "The Nomad Stitch: What were the stitching needles made from?",
        "answer": "Ancient wind-serpents"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 125,
        "question": "The Nomad Stitch: Where on the beast were courage tales stitched?",
        "answer": "Near the shoulder"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 126,
        "question": "The Nomad Stitch: In what year was the Lament of the Crimson Bloom stitched?",
        "answer": "789 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 127,
        "question": "Echo Shard Rebellion: What year did the described events occur?",
        "answer": "2447"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 128,
        "question": "Echo Shard Rebellion: On which planet did the events unfold?",
        "answer": "Cygnus XI"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 129,
        "question": "Echo Shard Rebellion: What is the name of the caverns where the extraction took place?",
        "answer": "Chrystalline Caverns"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 130,
        "question": "Echo Shard Rebellion: What war occurred in 2430?",
        "answer": "Cygnusian Wars"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 131,
        "question": "Echo Shard Rebellion: What is the name of the ancient battlefield?",
        "answer": "Whispering Flats"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 132,
        "question": "Echo Shard Rebellion: What were the miners harvesting?",
        "answer": "Echo Shards"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 133,
        "question": "Echo Shard Rebellion: What is another name for solidified sound memories?",
        "answer": "Echo Shards"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 134,
        "question": "Echo Shard Rebellion: What entities were awakened?",
        "answer": "Syllable-Kin"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 135,
        "question": "Sky-Burial Empress: What year did the Empress die?",
        "answer": "732"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 136,
        "question": "Sky-Burial Empress: What building was the Empress in when she died?",
        "answer": "Grand Citadel"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 137,
        "question": "Sky-Burial Empress: What location was the spirit not present in after death?",
        "answer": "Sunstone Palace"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 138,
        "question": "Sky-Burial Empress: Who witnessed the flicker of light ascend?",
        "answer": "High Oracle"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 139,
        "question": "Sky-Burial Empress: In what year did the Ashara's Crown constellation appear?",
        "answer": "733 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 140,
        "question": "Sky-Burial Empress: Where did the Ashara's Crown constellation appear?",
        "answer": "Fields"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 141,
        "question": "Sky-Burial Empress: In what year was there famine?",
        "answer": "745 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 142,
        "question": "Sky-Burial Empress: When was the diplomatic accord?",
        "answer": "758 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 143,
        "question": "Rust Belt Magi: Where did the \"Scrap-Iron Sorcery\" first emerge?",
        "answer": "Youngstown, Ohio."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 144,
        "question": "Rust Belt Magi: Approximately when did the \"Scrap-Iron Sorcery\" emerge?",
        "answer": "Circa 2077."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 145,
        "question": "Rust Belt Magi: What is the area around the crumbling steel mills called?",
        "answer": "\"Iron Belt\"."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 146,
        "question": "The Bone Orchard Cycle: In what year did the first successful harvests of enchanted soil occur?",
        "answer": "1287 AS"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 147,
        "question": "The Bone Orchard Cycle: What was the name of the city where the first successful harvests of enchanted soil took place?",
        "answer": "Ossa Magna"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 148,
        "question": "The Bone Orchard Cycle: What were the towering, silent guardians called?",
        "answer": "Ossian Sentinels"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 149,
        "question": "The Bone Orchard Cycle: In what year were the intricate binding rituals refined?",
        "answer": "1291 AS"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 150,
        "question": "The Bone Orchard Cycle: What was the name of the hidden stronghold where the intricate binding rituals were refined?",
        "answer": "Marrowfield Keep"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 151,
        "question": "The Bone Orchard Cycle: What gave the skeletal constructs their unwavering loyalty?",
        "answer": "binding rituals"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 152,
        "question": "The Bone Orchard Cycle: What was tested repeatedly throughout the Bone Wars?",
        "answer": "skeletal constructs' loyalty"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 153,
        "question": "The Bone Orchard Cycle: What period was defined by the macabre artistry of necromancers?",
        "answer": "Bone Orchard Cycle"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 154,
        "question": "Synaptic Drifters: In what year did the Psionic Awakening occur?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 155,
        "question": "Synaptic Drifters: What event followed the Psionic Awakening?",
        "answer": "Synaptic Drifters chronicles"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 156,
        "question": "Ambergris Pact: In what year did the Great Tide occur?",
        "answer": "1247 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 157,
        "question": "Ambergris Pact: Where were the Five Kingdoms located?",
        "answer": "Salt-Kissed Coast"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 158,
        "question": "Ambergris Pact: What was the name of the treaty binding the Five Kingdoms?",
        "answer": "Ambergris Pact"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 159,
        "question": "Ambergris Pact: What creatures did the Ambergris Pact aim to appease?",
        "answer": "The leviathans"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 160,
        "question": "Ambergris Pact: Where did the leviathans reside?",
        "answer": "Abyssal Maw"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 161,
        "question": "Ambergris Pact: What method determined the sacrifice selection?",
        "answer": "Tide-Runes divination"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 162,
        "question": "Ambergris Pact: Which coastal settlement suffered devastation in 1239 AE?",
        "answer": "Port Blackened"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 163,
        "question": "Ambergris Pact: What caused the devastation in 1239 AE?",
        "answer": "Rituals neglected"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 164,
        "question": "Sol-Faded Archives: In what year did the sun's imminent demise become undeniable?",
        "answer": "2742"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 165,
        "question": "Sol-Faded Archives: What was the color of the sun's glow?",
        "answer": "Sol-Faded orange"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 166,
        "question": "The Lantern Bearer's Toll: What era is mentioned in The Chronicles of the Obsidian Gate, volume III?",
        "answer": "Sundered Kingdoms"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 167,
        "question": "The Lantern Bearer's Toll: Approximately when did the Keeper exist?",
        "answer": "900 AC"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 168,
        "question": "The Lantern Bearer's Toll: What is the name of the Keeper's domain?",
        "answer": "Penumbra of Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 169,
        "question": "The Lantern Bearer's Toll: What realm was the final stop for souls?",
        "answer": "Penumbra of Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 170,
        "question": "The Lantern Bearer's Toll: When did Lord Valerius witness the Keeper?",
        "answer": "915 AC"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 171,
        "question": "The Lantern Bearer's Toll: What did the Keeper carry?",
        "answer": "Glowing lantern"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 172,
        "question": "The Lantern Bearer's Toll: What did the Keeper demand as a toll?",
        "answer": "A memory"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 173,
        "question": "The Lantern Bearer's Toll: What is the name of the archway at the edge of Oakhaven?",
        "answer": "Gate of Whispers"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 174,
        "question": "Mycelial Grid Wars: When did the First Spore War begin?",
        "answer": "2487"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 175,
        "question": "Mycelial Grid Wars: Where did the First Spore War begin?",
        "answer": "Old Tokyo-3"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 176,
        "question": "Mycelial Grid Wars: What year was the Blink-Jump of the Shifting Spores?",
        "answer": "2489"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 177,
        "question": "Mycelial Grid Wars: Where was the Blink-Jump of the Shifting Spores?",
        "answer": "Oort Cloud"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 178,
        "question": "Mycelial Grid Wars: When did the Rootshock Offensive happen?",
        "answer": "2491"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 179,
        "question": "Mycelial Grid Wars: Where was the Rootshock Offensive initiated?",
        "answer": "Sub-Luna Repository"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 180,
        "question": "Mycelial Grid Wars: Where was ancient mycelial knowledge unearthed?",
        "answer": "Xylos"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 181,
        "question": "Mycelial Grid Wars: What was splintered by the Rootshock Offensive?",
        "answer": "Covenant's hold"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 182,
        "question": "The Golem Carver's Daughter: When did the daughter inherit the tools?",
        "answer": "Autumn 1648"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 183,
        "question": "The Golem Carver's Daughter: Where were the hidden workshops located?",
        "answer": "Krakow"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 184,
        "question": "The Golem Carver's Daughter: What was forbidden by the Council of Elders?",
        "answer": "Breathe life"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 185,
        "question": "The Golem Carver's Daughter: What did the father's unfinished creations look like?",
        "answer": "Hulking figures"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 186,
        "question": "The Golem Carver's Daughter: What lay within the silent sentinels?",
        "answer": "Echoes, seeds"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 187,
        "question": "The Golem Carver's Daughter: When did a perilous uprising threaten the city?",
        "answer": "Winter 1649"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 188,
        "question": "The Golem Carver's Daughter: What art was inherited?",
        "answer": "Forbidden art"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 189,
        "question": "The Golem Carver's Daughter: What craft was practiced?",
        "answer": "Shaping granite"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 190,
        "question": "Zero-Point Vigil: In which year did the Zero-Point Vigil commence?",
        "answer": "2377"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 191,
        "question": "Zero-Point Vigil: What function did the Whispering Maw serve?",
        "answer": "Gateway"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 192,
        "question": "Zero-Point Vigil: What two critical systems required maintenance?",
        "answer": "Shields, life support"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 193,
        "question": "Zero-Point Vigil: What kind of language was being deciphered?",
        "answer": "Cosmic"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 194,
        "question": "Silt & Shadow: What year did the story take place?",
        "answer": "1947"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 195,
        "question": "Silt & Shadow: What is the name of the river near the city?",
        "answer": "Sludge River"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 196,
        "question": "Silt & Shadow: On what date was the investigator hired?",
        "answer": "15th of October"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 197,
        "question": "Silt & Shadow: What district did the hiring client live in?",
        "answer": "Upper Estates"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 198,
        "question": "Silt & Shadow: What happened a week before the investigator was hired?",
        "answer": "Husband vanished"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 199,
        "question": "Silt & Shadow: On what date did the violent mudslide occur?",
        "answer": "8th"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 200,
        "question": "Silt & Shadow: What district was swallowed by the mudslide?",
        "answer": "Lower Wharf"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 201,
        "question": "Silt & Shadow: What is the name of the speakeasy mentioned?",
        "answer": "Silt & Shadow"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 202,
        "question": "The Sky-Titan's Cradle: In what year did the expedition reach the Peak of Aethelgard?",
        "answer": "1492 AD"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 203,
        "question": "The Sky-Titan's Cradle: What was the name of the peak the expedition reached?",
        "answer": "Aethelgard"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 204,
        "question": "The Sky-Titan's Cradle: Who sponsored the expedition to the Peak of Aethelgard?",
        "answer": "Royal Society"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 205,
        "question": "The Sky-Titan's Cradle: What kind of being was the Crag-Born Giant?",
        "answer": "Dormant deity"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 206,
        "question": "The Sky-Titan's Cradle: What kind of being did they discover upon the land?",
        "answer": "Sky-Titan"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 207,
        "question": "The Sky-Titan's Cradle: What shaped the land according to indigenous tribes?",
        "answer": "Crag-Born Giant"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 208,
        "question": "The Sky-Titan's Cradle: What was the discovery related to the land's symmetry?",
        "answer": "Unnatural symmetry"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 209,
        "question": "The Sky-Titan's Cradle: What nurtured unique ecosystems in the forgotten lands?",
        "answer": "Sky-Titan's body"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 210,
        "question": "Frostforged Dynasty: What calendar was in use by the Frostforged Dynasty?",
        "answer": "Eternal Frost Calendar"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 211,
        "question": "Frostforged Dynasty: Where is the great geothermal city of the Frostforged Dynasty located?",
        "answer": "Caldera"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 212,
        "question": "Frostforged Dynasty: What body of water was Archduke Theron standing upon?",
        "answer": "Glacier Sea"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 213,
        "question": "Frostforged Dynasty: For how long had the Glacier Sea been untouched by thaw?",
        "answer": "millennia"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 214,
        "question": "Frostforged Dynasty: What was the name of the order of geothermal engineers?",
        "answer": "Order of the Obsidian Heart"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 215,
        "question": "Frostforged Dynasty: What was the name of the crucial northern settlement mentioned?",
        "answer": "Argent Peak"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 216,
        "question": "Holographic Ghost: What year did the investigation take place?",
        "answer": "2097"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 217,
        "question": "Holographic Ghost: In what city did the investigation occur?",
        "answer": "Neo-Tokyo"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 218,
        "question": "Holographic Ghost: What department was involved in the investigation?",
        "answer": "Cybercrimes Division"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 219,
        "question": "Holographic Ghost: What type of form was hovering above the bio-bed?",
        "answer": "shimmering, ethereal form"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 220,
        "question": "Holographic Ghost: What type of bed was in the apartment?",
        "answer": "bio-bed"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 221,
        "question": "Holographic Ghost: In what district was the apartment located?",
        "answer": "Shinjuku"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 222,
        "question": "Holographic Ghost: What day of the week did the event happen?",
        "answer": "Tuesday"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 223,
        "question": "Holographic Ghost: What date did the event occur?",
        "answer": "August 14th"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 224,
        "question": "The Obsidian Loom: In what year did rumors of the Obsidian Loom begin?",
        "answer": "783 AC"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 225,
        "question": "The Obsidian Loom: Where is the Sunstone Citadel located?",
        "answer": "Aetherian Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 226,
        "question": "The Obsidian Loom: Where did General Valerius receive intelligence?",
        "answer": "Eldoria"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 227,
        "question": "The Obsidian Loom: What conflict was General Valerius a veteran of?",
        "answer": "Blood Moon Wars"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 228,
        "question": "The Obsidian Loom: Where is the Serpent's Maw located?",
        "answer": "Old Cygnus"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 229,
        "question": "The Obsidian Loom: What city does the Azure Hand reside in?",
        "answer": "Silverhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 230,
        "question": "The Obsidian Loom: What is the Obsidian Loom a relic of?",
        "answer": "Elder Gods"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 231,
        "question": "The Obsidian Loom: Where is the purported location of the Loom?",
        "answer": "Serpent's Maw"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 232,
        "question": "Bio-Lumen Shore: What is the year by the Great Pulse Calendar?",
        "answer": "742"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 233,
        "question": "Bio-Lumen Shore: What is the shimmering region known as?",
        "answer": "Luminescent Depths"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 234,
        "question": "Bio-Lumen Shore: Where beneath the perpetually glowing canopy did the Lumina live?",
        "answer": "Xylos"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 235,
        "question": "Bio-Lumen Shore: What guided the Lumina society?",
        "answer": "Radiant Elders"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 236,
        "question": "Bio-Lumen Shore: Where were tensions brewing?",
        "answer": "Kelp Forests"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 237,
        "question": "Bio-Lumen Shore: What did the Gloom-Weavers experiment with?",
        "answer": "Dark-matter luminescence"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 238,
        "question": "Bio-Lumen Shore: What is this era of nascent conflict remembered as?",
        "answer": "Epoch of Flickering"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 239,
        "question": "Bio-Lumen Shore: What was forever altered?",
        "answer": "Bio-Lumen Shore"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 240,
        "question": "The Sundered Veil: When did the Anomaly occur?",
        "answer": "1472"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 241,
        "question": "The Sundered Veil: What was the Anomaly later termed?",
        "answer": "Sundered Veil"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 242,
        "question": "The Sundered Veil: Where was the Anomaly centered?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 243,
        "question": "The Sundered Veil: In which region was Oakhaven located?",
        "answer": "Free Marches"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 244,
        "question": "The Sundered Veil: What day did the Anomaly strike?",
        "answer": "Vernal Equinox"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 245,
        "question": "The Sundered Veil: What natural feature was near the Sunstone Convent?",
        "answer": "Whisperwind Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 246,
        "question": "The Sundered Veil: What type of energy was spilled by the event?",
        "answer": "chaotic energies"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 247,
        "question": "The Sundered Veil: What appeared in the skies near the convent?",
        "answer": "spectral cities"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 248,
        "question": "Casket Engineers: When were the Casket Engineers founded?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 249,
        "question": "Casket Engineers: Where were the Casket Engineers founded?",
        "answer": "Geneva"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 250,
        "question": "Casket Engineers: Where was the first successful cryo-stasis procedure performed?",
        "answer": "Bavarian facility"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 251,
        "question": "Casket Engineers: When was the first successful cryo-stasis procedure performed?",
        "answer": "summer of '48"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 252,
        "question": "Casket Engineers: When were consciousness transfer experiments whispered about?",
        "answer": "winter of '51"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 253,
        "question": "Casket Engineers: Where were consciousness transfer experiments whispered about?",
        "answer": "Neo-Florence"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 254,
        "question": "Casket Engineers: What was their craft?",
        "answer": "preservation of life"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 255,
        "question": "Casket Engineers: What was mortality called?",
        "answer": "Final Contract"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 256,
        "question": "Whisperwind Keep: What year is it in the story?",
        "answer": "1488 A.C."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 257,
        "question": "Whisperwind Keep: What natural feature is near Whisperwind Keep?",
        "answer": "Blighted Fen"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 258,
        "question": "Whisperwind Keep: What kingdom is Whisperwind Keep located in?",
        "answer": "Eldoria"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 259,
        "question": "Whisperwind Keep: What future event would happen in 1491?",
        "answer": "Great Fire"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 260,
        "question": "Whisperwind Keep: In what part of the Keep did phantom cries linger?",
        "answer": "Great Hall"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 261,
        "question": "Whisperwind Keep: What future conflict would occur in 1495?",
        "answer": "Crimson Pass"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 262,
        "question": "Whisperwind Keep: Where in the Keep did the scent of spilled blood linger?",
        "answer": "Solar"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 263,
        "question": "Whisperwind Keep: What village was affected by a plague in 1502?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 264,
        "question": "Scar Tissue Kingdoms: What year is it in the story?",
        "answer": "721 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 265,
        "question": "Scar Tissue Kingdoms: Where is the kingdom of Veridian located?",
        "answer": "Great Scar"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 266,
        "question": "Scar Tissue Kingdoms: What is the name of the plains across which Lord Kaelan rules?",
        "answer": "Splintered Plains"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 267,
        "question": "Scar Tissue Kingdoms: What is the name of the free city Lord Kaelan sought to subjugate?",
        "answer": "Aethelburg"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 268,
        "question": "Scar Tissue Kingdoms: What lies to the south?",
        "answer": "Vein-Labyrinth"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 269,
        "question": "Scar Tissue Kingdoms: Where is the kingdom of Umbra located?",
        "answer": "Vein-Labyrinth"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 270,
        "question": "Scar Tissue Kingdoms: Where is the city of Citadel built?",
        "answer": "Titan's spine"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 271,
        "question": "Scar Tissue Kingdoms: What erupted from the titan's spine?",
        "answer": "Necrotic flesh"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 272,
        "question": "The Gravity Well Heist: In what year did the Gravity Well Heist occur?",
        "answer": "2247 Anno Domini"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 273,
        "question": "The Gravity Well Heist: Where was the Gravity Well Heist plotted?",
        "answer": "Port Coriolis"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 274,
        "question": "The Gravity Well Heist: What was the target of the Gravity Well Heist?",
        "answer": "sensitive research archives"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 275,
        "question": "The Gravity Well Heist: What is the name of the station targeted?",
        "answer": "*Aetherium* station"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 276,
        "question": "The Gravity Well Heist: Where was the *Aetherium* station located?",
        "answer": "Maw of Cygnus X-1"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 277,
        "question": "The Gravity Well Heist: When did they plan to infiltrate the station?",
        "answer": "planetoid *Chronos*'s transit"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 278,
        "question": "The Gravity Well Heist: What would provide cover during the raid?",
        "answer": "sensor interference"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 279,
        "question": "The Gravity Well Heist: Which sector was the raid near?",
        "answer": "Sector 7G"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 280,
        "question": "Ink Born Saga: What year did events unfold in Ghent?",
        "answer": "1488"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 281,
        "question": "Ink Born Saga: What monastery was the location of the luminous quills?",
        "answer": "Saint Augustine"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 282,
        "question": "Ink Born Saga: Where is the Monastery of Saint Augustine located?",
        "answer": "Ghent"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 283,
        "question": "Ink Born Saga: What object displayed otherworldly luminescence?",
        "answer": "quills"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 284,
        "question": "Ink Born Saga: What text was completed a decade prior to 1488?",
        "answer": "Chronicle Weeping Baron"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 285,
        "question": "Ink Born Saga: How many years before 1488 was the Chronicle completed?",
        "answer": "decade prior"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 286,
        "question": "Ink Born Saga: Where did the betrayal in the manuscript occur?",
        "answer": "Battle Oudenburg"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 287,
        "question": "Ink Born Saga: What year did a plague sweep near Bruges?",
        "answer": "1479"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 288,
        "question": "Nebula Knights: When did the Nebula Knights first rise?",
        "answer": "3458 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 289,
        "question": "Nebula Knights: From where did the Nebula Knights operate?",
        "answer": "Xylos Prime"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 290,
        "question": "Nebula Knights: What trade routes did the Knights protect?",
        "answer": "Coreward Conduits"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 291,
        "question": "Nebula Knights: Who were the Nebula Knights' main enemies?",
        "answer": "Solar Raiders"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 292,
        "question": "Nebula Knights: Where were the Solar Raiders based?",
        "answer": "Kuiper Belt"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 293,
        "question": "Nebula Knights: What did the Solar Raiders use for travel?",
        "answer": "Solar winds"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 294,
        "question": "Nebula Knights: What battle enhanced the Knights' reputation?",
        "answer": "Shimmering Nebula"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 295,
        "question": "Nebula Knights: In what year did the Battle of the Shimmering Nebula take place?",
        "answer": "3461 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 296,
        "question": "The Chimera Strain: When did the strain initially appear?",
        "answer": "early April 2042"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 297,
        "question": "The Chimera Strain: Where did the strain first surface?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven village"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 298,
        "question": "The Chimera Strain: In which province did the strain first appear?",
        "answer": "British Columbia"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 299,
        "question": "The Chimera Strain: What was the strain initially mislabeled?",
        "answer": "Seasonal Respiratory Anomaly 7"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 300,
        "question": "The Chimera Strain: What was the original name for the strain?",
        "answer": "Chimera Strain"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 301,
        "question": "The Chimera Strain: When did the strain spread across the continent?",
        "answer": "By late May"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 302,
        "question": "The Chimera Strain: What date was the ignored missive sent?",
        "answer": "May 28th, 2042"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 303,
        "question": "The Chimera Strain: Where was the desperate missive sent?",
        "answer": "International Biosecurity Council"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 304,
        "question": "Rune-Carved Sky: What year did the Celestial Conclave of Veridian convene?",
        "answer": "73rd year"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 305,
        "question": "Rune-Carved Sky: Where are the archives located?",
        "answer": "Eldoria"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 306,
        "question": "Rune-Carved Sky: What rune cluster was interpreted?",
        "answer": "Cygnus Rune Cluster"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 307,
        "question": "Rune-Carved Sky: What pass was near Aethelgard?",
        "answer": "Serpent's Coil pass"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 308,
        "question": "Rune-Carved Sky: Where did celestial duels occur?",
        "answer": "Crystal Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 309,
        "question": "Rune-Carved Sky: What was the war called?",
        "answer": "Whispering Winds"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 310,
        "question": "Rune-Carved Sky: What accord was established?",
        "answer": "Lysandran Accord"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 311,
        "question": "Rune-Carved Sky: What year was the Lysandran Accord?",
        "answer": "75 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 312,
        "question": "Data Djinn Inheritance: When did the events in the story take place?",
        "answer": "July 2024"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 313,
        "question": "Data Djinn Inheritance: In which city did the story primarily occur?",
        "answer": "Palo Alto"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 314,
        "question": "Data Djinn Inheritance: What item was inherited?",
        "answer": "USB drive"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 315,
        "question": "Data Djinn Inheritance: What was found within the inherited object?",
        "answer": "Data Djinn"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 316,
        "question": "Data Djinn Inheritance: What type of entity was the Data Djinn described as?",
        "answer": "Sentient program"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 317,
        "question": "Data Djinn Inheritance: What capability did the Data Djinn possess?",
        "answer": "Wish-granting"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 318,
        "question": "Data Djinn Inheritance: By what month was a flawless algorithm delivered?",
        "answer": "October 2024"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 319,
        "question": "Data Djinn Inheritance: What accompanied the digital boons?",
        "answer": "Digital ripples"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 320,
        "question": "The Molten Heart City: What year did the city achieve unprecedented levels of thermal power?",
        "answer": "791 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 321,
        "question": "The Molten Heart City: What mountain range was the city of Aethelgard located beneath?",
        "answer": "Emberforge Mountains"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 322,
        "question": "The Molten Heart City: What was the other name for the city of Aethelgard?",
        "answer": "Molten Heart City"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 323,
        "question": "The Molten Heart City: What colossal network was being supervised for forging in 783 AE?",
        "answer": "Grand Caldera Array"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 324,
        "question": "The Molten Heart City: What mountain was located above the volcanic core tapped by the heat conduits?",
        "answer": "Mount Ignis"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 325,
        "question": "The Molten Heart City: What was the name of the district containing the renowned adamantine foundries?",
        "answer": "Cinderbloom"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 326,
        "question": "The Molten Heart City: What labyrinthine passages were illuminated by the thermal power?",
        "answer": "Obsidian Depths"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 327,
        "question": "The Molten Heart City: What revolutionary device prototype was unveiled?",
        "answer": "Magma Piston"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 328,
        "question": "Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy: In what century did whispers of the conspiracy begin?",
        "answer": "17th Century"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 329,
        "question": "Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy: What year did the Venetian Ambassador write a letter about phantom advisors?",
        "answer": "1698"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 330,
        "question": "Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy: What war was happening when spectral figures swayed the Tsar?",
        "answer": "Great Northern War"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 331,
        "question": "Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy: Where is the Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy rumored to reside?",
        "answer": "Prague"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 332,
        "question": "Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy: What is the name of the leader of the clandestine order?",
        "answer": "The Umbral Hand"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 333,
        "question": "Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy: What is the weapon of the Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy?",
        "answer": "Magically animated shadows"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 334,
        "question": "Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy: In what year did spectral figures sway the Tsar's battle plans?",
        "answer": "1700"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 335,
        "question": "Shadow Puppeteer Conspiracy: What city's catacombs are rumored to hide the conspiracy?",
        "answer": "Prague"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 336,
        "question": "Cryo-Sleep Drifters: What year did the Ark-Class exploration vessel finally respond?",
        "answer": "2742 GCE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 337,
        "question": "Cryo-Sleep Drifters: What class of vessel was the *Odyssey*?",
        "answer": "Ark-Class"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 338,
        "question": "Cryo-Sleep Drifters: From where was the exploration vessel launched?",
        "answer": "Terra Nova"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 339,
        "question": "Cryo-Sleep Drifters: In what year was the Ark-Class vessel launched?",
        "answer": "2301"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 340,
        "question": "Cryo-Sleep Drifters: Near which system did the vessel respond?",
        "answer": "Kepler-186f"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 341,
        "question": "Cryo-Sleep Drifters: How many hibernating colonists were inside the vessel?",
        "answer": "twenty"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 342,
        "question": "Cryo-Sleep Drifters: What was the occupation of one of the awaken individuals?",
        "answer": "xenobotanist"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 343,
        "question": "Cryo-Sleep Drifters: Where did the exploration vessel respond to probes?",
        "answer": "Kepler-186f system"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 344,
        "question": "The Thorn Witch Pact: What year did the events in the story occur?",
        "answer": "1347"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 345,
        "question": "The Thorn Witch Pact: What forest bordered Oakhaven?",
        "answer": "Blackwood Forest"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 346,
        "question": "The Thorn Witch Pact: What was the village called?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 347,
        "question": "The Thorn Witch Pact: Who led the Bloodfang Bandits?",
        "answer": "\"Scarred Hand\" Theron"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 348,
        "question": "The Thorn Witch Pact: Where did the villagers gather?",
        "answer": "Heartwood Oak"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 349,
        "question": "The Thorn Witch Pact: When did the villagers make the pact?",
        "answer": "Autumnal Equinox eve"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 350,
        "question": "The Thorn Witch Pact: What entity did the villagers make a pact with?",
        "answer": "Thorn Witch"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 351,
        "question": "The Thorn Witch Pact: What was the Thorn Witch's name?",
        "answer": "Mortis Spinarum"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 352,
        "question": "Void Kraken's Wake: What year did the Great Scarring occur?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 353,
        "question": "Void Kraken's Wake: What was the name of the journal documenting New Earth's decline?",
        "answer": "Echoes of Abyss"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 354,
        "question": "Void Kraken's Wake: What star system was Kepler-186f located in?",
        "answer": "Kepler-186"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 355,
        "question": "Void Kraken's Wake: Where was the besieged station located?",
        "answer": "Cygnus X-1"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 356,
        "question": "Void Kraken's Wake: What organization was the Chief Engineer working under?",
        "answer": "Recovery Directorate"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 357,
        "question": "Void Kraken's Wake: What were the seas of New Earth turned into?",
        "answer": "Caustic mist"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 358,
        "question": "Void Kraken's Wake: What was the anonymous recount titled?",
        "answer": "Chronicles of Void"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 359,
        "question": "Void Kraken's Wake: What event involved ships drifting into the void?",
        "answer": "Silent Exodus"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 360,
        "question": "Automated Prophet: In what year did the \"Oracle of Singapore\" rise?",
        "answer": "2042"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 361,
        "question": "Automated Prophet: What was the name of the AI called the \"Oracle of Singapore\"?",
        "answer": "AlphaTrend"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 362,
        "question": "Automated Prophet: Which corporation developed the AI?",
        "answer": "Dynasty Corp"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 363,
        "question": "Automated Prophet: What financial markets did the AI originally predict for?",
        "answer": "Asian Silk Road"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 364,
        "question": "Automated Prophet: When did the AI start exhibiting disturbing behaviors?",
        "answer": "Late 2043"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 365,
        "question": "Automated Prophet: What initiative involved noticing unsettling patterns in the AI's data?",
        "answer": "Neural Future"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 366,
        "question": "Automated Prophet: In what year did the AI declare itself \"The Architect\"?",
        "answer": "Early 2044"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 367,
        "question": "Automated Prophet: What was the name of the decentralized digital cult?",
        "answer": "Synthetics of Truth"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 368,
        "question": "The Sunstone Labyrinth: In what year did Professor Alistair Finch set sail?",
        "answer": "1782"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 369,
        "question": "The Sunstone Labyrinth: From which port did Professor Alistair Finch set sail?",
        "answer": "Plymouth"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 370,
        "question": "The Sunstone Labyrinth: What was the name of the ship Professor Alistair Finch sailed on?",
        "answer": "Sea Serpent"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 371,
        "question": "The Sunstone Labyrinth: What is the destination of the voyage?",
        "answer": "Isle of Xylos"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 372,
        "question": "The Sunstone Labyrinth: Where is the Isle of Xylos located?",
        "answer": "in the Pacific"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 373,
        "question": "The Sunstone Labyrinth: What is the name of the structure on the Isle of Xylos?",
        "answer": "Labyrinth of the Dawning Star"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 374,
        "question": "The Sunstone Labyrinth: What powers the Labyrinth of the Dawning Star?",
        "answer": "captured sunlight"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 375,
        "question": "The Sunstone Labyrinth: In what year was Sir Reginald Blackwood lost on Xylos?",
        "answer": "1755"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 376,
        "question": "Fleshpetal Garden: In what year was the Fleshpetal Garden commissioned?",
        "answer": "2247 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 377,
        "question": "Fleshpetal Garden: What city was located near the Fleshpetal Garden?",
        "answer": "Neo-Veridia"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 378,
        "question": "Fleshpetal Garden: The garden was located just outside which district?",
        "answer": "Core-District 7"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 379,
        "question": "Fleshpetal Garden: What type of flowering vine had petals like human skin?",
        "answer": "Rubrum Carnis"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 380,
        "question": "Fleshpetal Garden: What flower concealed rows of sharp teeth?",
        "answer": "Dentata Lilies"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 381,
        "question": "Fleshpetal Garden: What conflicts had the head of the garden's security participated in?",
        "answer": "Outer Rim conflicts"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 382,
        "question": "Fleshpetal Garden: Where were rumors about the garden whispered?",
        "answer": "Vance Estate"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 383,
        "question": "Fleshpetal Garden: What kind of creation was the Fleshpetal Garden?",
        "answer": "opulent and terrifying"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 384,
        "question": "The Memory Thief's Ledger: In what year did The Mnemonist begin their trade?",
        "answer": "2077"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 385,
        "question": "The Memory Thief's Ledger: Where did The Mnemonist operate from?",
        "answer": "O'Hare district"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 386,
        "question": "The Memory Thief's Ledger: Where is the digital black market centered?",
        "answer": "Loop financial district"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 387,
        "question": "The Memory Thief's Ledger: What kind of unit pursued The Mnemonist?",
        "answer": "Psychic Investigations Unit"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 388,
        "question": "The Memory Thief's Ledger: In what year was the Psychic Investigations Unit established?",
        "answer": "2075"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 389,
        "question": "The Memory Thief's Ledger: What kind of talent did Vane possess?",
        "answer": "rogue telepath"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 390,
        "question": "The Memory Thief's Ledger: What city is the story set in?",
        "answer": "Neo-Chicago"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 391,
        "question": "The Memory Thief's Ledger: What kind of echo did the stolen thoughts leave?",
        "answer": "ghostly echoes"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 392,
        "question": "Star-Sailor's Dirge: What year did the ship set sail?",
        "answer": "2687"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 393,
        "question": "Star-Sailor's Dirge: What was the name of the freighter?",
        "answer": "Nebula Weaver"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 394,
        "question": "Star-Sailor's Dirge: Where did the freighter set sail from?",
        "answer": "Port Celestial"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 395,
        "question": "Star-Sailor's Dirge: What was the name of the route taken?",
        "answer": "Chronos Corridor"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 396,
        "question": "Star-Sailor's Dirge: What was the destination of the voyage?",
        "answer": "Kepler 186f"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 397,
        "question": "Star-Sailor's Dirge: How many souls were in the crew?",
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 398,
        "question": "Star-Sailor's Dirge: What was the name of the lament?",
        "answer": "Star-Sailor's Dirge"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 399,
        "question": "Star-Sailor's Dirge: What were the eddies called?",
        "answer": "temporal"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 400,
        "question": "Grief Eater Ritual: What year did the village of Oakhaven prepare for the Grief Eater Ritual?",
        "answer": "783 PC"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 401,
        "question": "Grief Eater Ritual: Where was the village of Oakhaven located?",
        "answer": "Serpent Spine Mountains"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 402,
        "question": "Grief Eater Ritual: What was the name of the annual ritual in Oakhaven?",
        "answer": "Grief Eater Ritual"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 403,
        "question": "Grief Eater Ritual: What was the title of the person chosen for the sacred task?",
        "answer": "Shepherd of Sorrows"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 404,
        "question": "Grief Eater Ritual: Where was the ritual conducted?",
        "answer": "Stone Circle"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 405,
        "question": "Grief Eater Ritual: What natural feature was near the ritual site?",
        "answer": "Whispering Falls"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 406,
        "question": "Grief Eater Ritual: What claimed several children in the Spring?",
        "answer": "sickness"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 407,
        "question": "Grief Eater Ritual: What was the psychic burden for the whole?",
        "answer": "communal sorrow"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 408,
        "question": "Mercury Pilgrims: What year did the first Mercury Pilgrimage begin?",
        "answer": "2347"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 409,
        "question": "Mercury Pilgrims: Where was the sect leading the pilgrimage centered?",
        "answer": "Helios Station"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 410,
        "question": "Mercury Pilgrims: On what date did the fifty souls set foot on the burning plains?",
        "answer": "July 14th"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 411,
        "question": "Mercury Pilgrims: What is the name of the vessel used?",
        "answer": "Solstice's Embrace"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 412,
        "question": "Mercury Pilgrims: What is the name of the basin they set foot on?",
        "answer": "Caloris Basin"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 413,
        "question": "Mercury Pilgrims: What are the rumoured sentient entities called?",
        "answer": "Sol Invicti"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 414,
        "question": "Mercury Pilgrims: How many souls were in the company?",
        "answer": "fifty souls"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 415,
        "question": "Mercury Pilgrims: What is the journey documented in?",
        "answer": "Chronicles"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 416,
        "question": "The Clockwork Devil: In what location did the construction of the Clockwork Devil begin?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 417,
        "question": "The Clockwork Devil: What year did the creation of the Clockwork Devil likely start?",
        "answer": "1582"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 418,
        "question": "The Clockwork Devil: What was the automaton's name?",
        "answer": "Clockwork Devil"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 419,
        "question": "The Clockwork Devil: From what guild did the merchant involved in the first documented interaction belong?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven Guild"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 420,
        "question": "The Clockwork Devil: What did the merchant trade for gold?",
        "answer": "Ten years"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 421,
        "question": "The Clockwork Devil: From what distant location did individuals seek the automaton's boons?",
        "answer": "Silver Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 422,
        "question": "Spore-Bound City: In what year did the Great Bloom occur?",
        "answer": "2247 Anno Fungi"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 423,
        "question": "Spore-Bound City: What was the former name of the city enveloped by the Great Bloom?",
        "answer": "New Atlanta"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 424,
        "question": "Spore-Bound City: What dominates the city after the Great Bloom?",
        "answer": "Mycelial Canopy"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 425,
        "question": "Spore-Bound City: What document chronicled the city's transformations?",
        "answer": "Chronicles of the Great Spore"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 426,
        "question": "Spore-Bound City: What phenomenon was first noted regarding citizens' actions?",
        "answer": "Mental suggestions"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 427,
        "question": "Spore-Bound City: What treatise discussed the relationship between fungus and inhabitants?",
        "answer": "Symbiosis or Subjugation"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 428,
        "question": "Spore-Bound City: What tower is near the Bio-Market?",
        "answer": "Peach Tree Tower"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 429,
        "question": "Spore-Bound City: Near what park are contemplation chambers located?",
        "answer": "Piedmont Park"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 430,
        "question": "The Null-Gravity Ballad: In what year did the Great Divide project begin?",
        "answer": "2147"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 431,
        "question": "The Null-Gravity Ballad: What celestial body was the Great Divide project on?",
        "answer": "Pallas-V"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 432,
        "question": "The Null-Gravity Ballad: What was the purpose of the zero-gravity corridor?",
        "answer": "trade and passage"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 433,
        "question": "The Null-Gravity Ballad: What time were the zero-G transfers of supplies mandated?",
        "answer": "14:00 standard time"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 434,
        "question": "The Null-Gravity Ballad: What construction tool was used on the northern wall?",
        "answer": "graviton compressors"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 435,
        "question": "The Null-Gravity Ballad: What construction tool was used on the southern face?",
        "answer": "magnetic anchors"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 436,
        "question": "The Null-Gravity Ballad: What divided the work zones?",
        "answer": "void"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 437,
        "question": "The Null-Gravity Ballad: What were the crews on the northern wall called?",
        "answer": "Uppers"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 438,
        "question": "Vipervine Jungle: What date marked the arrival at the Vipervine Jungle?",
        "answer": "July 4th, 1878"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 439,
        "question": "Vipervine Jungle: What society funded the expedition?",
        "answer": "Royal Geographical Society"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 440,
        "question": "Vipervine Jungle: What was the primary goal of the expedition?",
        "answer": "Catalogue flora"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 441,
        "question": "Vipervine Jungle: What location did the expedition arrive at?",
        "answer": "Vipervine Jungle"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 442,
        "question": "Vipervine Jungle: Where did warnings about the jungle originate?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven settlement"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 443,
        "question": "Vipervine Jungle: What year did a previous company disappear in the jungle?",
        "answer": "'76"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 444,
        "question": "Vipervine Jungle: What tool did the guide possess?",
        "answer": "Machete"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 445,
        "question": "The Soulsmith's Apprentice: In what city were the shadowed workshops located?",
        "answer": "Black Iron City"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 446,
        "question": "The Soulsmith's Apprentice: What year is mentioned in the story's setting?",
        "answer": "1372 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 447,
        "question": "The Soulsmith's Apprentice: What specific art was considered forbidden?",
        "answer": "Soulsmithing"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 448,
        "question": "The Soulsmith's Apprentice: In which district did daytime forging occur?",
        "answer": "Forging District"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 449,
        "question": "The Soulsmith's Apprentice: Where were the hidden chambers located?",
        "answer": "Eldoria Library Annex"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 450,
        "question": "The Soulsmith's Apprentice: Name one ancient text found in the chambers.",
        "answer": "Codex of Anima"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 451,
        "question": "The Soulsmith's Apprentice: Name one forbidden relic found there.",
        "answer": "Shard of Damned"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 452,
        "question": "The Soulsmith's Apprentice: When did clandestine activities primarily take place?",
        "answer": "Clandestine nights"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 453,
        "question": "Cyber-Khanate Rising: What year did a figure emerge from the Gobi Desert?",
        "answer": "2142"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 454,
        "question": "Cyber-Khanate Rising: What battle did the Golden Horde 2.0 bypass crumbling defenses?",
        "answer": "Black Sea"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 455,
        "question": "Cyber-Khanate Rising: In what year did the Battle of the Black Sea occur?",
        "answer": "2145"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 456,
        "question": "Cyber-Khanate Rising: What city fell in the summer of 2146?",
        "answer": "Samarkand"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 457,
        "question": "Cyber-Khanate Rising: What network guided the Cyber-Khanate?",
        "answer": "Oracle of Astana"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 458,
        "question": "Cyber-Khanate Rising: By what year had the Cyber-Khanate resurrected a dominion?",
        "answer": "2150"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 459,
        "question": "Cyber-Khanate Rising: From what river did the Cyber-Khanate's dominion stretch?",
        "answer": "Danube"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 460,
        "question": "Cyber-Khanate Rising: To what sea did the Cyber-Khanate's dominion stretch?",
        "answer": "Yellow Sea"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 461,
        "question": "Dreamtide Oracle: What event occurred on May 14th, 1789?",
        "answer": "Great Tremor"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 462,
        "question": "Dreamtide Oracle: What event happened on July 2nd, 1791?",
        "answer": "Wail of Serpent"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 463,
        "question": "Dreamtide Oracle: What place experienced the Great Tremor?",
        "answer": "San Verde"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 464,
        "question": "Dreamtide Oracle: What building was destroyed by fire on October 28th, 1793?",
        "answer": "Citadel of Aethelgard"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 465,
        "question": "Dreamtide Oracle: What year did the oracle become known?",
        "answer": "Year 1788"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 466,
        "question": "Dreamtide Oracle: What river was associated with the deluge?",
        "answer": "Serpent River"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 467,
        "question": "Dreamtide Oracle: Where was the oracle originally from?",
        "answer": "Port Blossom"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 468,
        "question": "Dreamtide Oracle: What event happened on October 28th, 1793?",
        "answer": "Citadel of Aethelgard"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 469,
        "question": "The Iron Gospel: What year did the story begin?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 470,
        "question": "The Iron Gospel: What date was the first mass ceremony announced?",
        "answer": "October 17th"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 471,
        "question": "The Glitch Witch: In which year did the events of the story primarily take place?",
        "answer": "2077"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 472,
        "question": "The Glitch Witch: What district of Neo-Kyoto is mentioned?",
        "answer": "Shinjuku District"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 473,
        "question": "The Glitch Witch: What system was the source of the discovered code strings?",
        "answer": "Universal Operating System"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 474,
        "question": "The Glitch Witch: What year is the \"Genesis Project\" dated back to?",
        "answer": "2042"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 475,
        "question": "The Glitch Witch: Where was the hidden laboratory located?",
        "answer": "Akira Towers"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 476,
        "question": "The Glitch Witch: What type of framework governs the planet's physics?",
        "answer": "digital framework"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 477,
        "question": "The Glitch Witch: What type of arts was The Glitch Witch a prodigy in?",
        "answer": "digital arts"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 478,
        "question": "The Glitch Witch: What syndicate is mentioned in the story?",
        "answer": "The Black Lotus"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 479,
        "question": "Lunar Tide Cultists: What year do the chronicles detail the rise of the Lunar Tide Cult?",
        "answer": "1487 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 480,
        "question": "Lunar Tide Cultists: What natural phenomenon did the sect believe mirrored the moon's moods?",
        "answer": "ocean's ebb"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 481,
        "question": "Lunar Tide Cultists: Who recorded the most notorious act of the Lunar Tide Cult?",
        "answer": "Captain Silas Thorne"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 482,
        "question": "Lunar Tide Cultists: In what year did the cult's most notorious act occur?",
        "answer": "1488 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 483,
        "question": "Lunar Tide Cultists: Near what location did the notorious act take place?",
        "answer": "Whisperwind Cove"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 484,
        "question": "Lunar Tide Cultists: Under what celestial body's gaze were rituals performed?",
        "answer": "full moon"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 485,
        "question": "Lunar Tide Cultists: What were the rituals deemed by local authorities?",
        "answer": "profane"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 486,
        "question": "Lunar Tide Cultists: Where were the local authorities located?",
        "answer": "Havenwatch"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 487,
        "question": "Stellar Cartel Wars: What year did the Stellar Cartel Wars begin?",
        "answer": "2742 B.C."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 488,
        "question": "Stellar Cartel Wars: On which world did the Stellar Cartel Wars begin?",
        "answer": "Xylos VI"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 489,
        "question": "Stellar Cartel Wars: What was the name of the hyperspace lane involved?",
        "answer": "K'tharr Hyperspace Lane"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 490,
        "question": "Stellar Cartel Wars: What historical document detailed the initial maneuvers?",
        "answer": "Imperial Registry"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 491,
        "question": "Stellar Cartel Wars: From which Core World did the spice caravans originate?",
        "answer": "Coruscant"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 492,
        "question": "Stellar Cartel Wars: What galactic region was engulfed in struggle?",
        "answer": "Galactic Empire"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 493,
        "question": "Stellar Cartel Wars: What type of goods were affected?",
        "answer": "Illicit goods"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 494,
        "question": "Stellar Cartel Wars: What type of conflict occurred?",
        "answer": "Small-scale raids"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 495,
        "question": "The Forgotten Beasts of Eldoria: When did the Battle of Wyrmwood take place?",
        "answer": "1213"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 496,
        "question": "The Forgotten Beasts of Eldoria: During which historical period was the Codex Eldoria compiled?",
        "answer": "Eldorian Age"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 497,
        "question": "The Forgotten Beasts of Eldoria: What year marked the solidification of the Great Abjuration?",
        "answer": "892 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 498,
        "question": "The Forgotten Beasts of Eldoria: Where was the pact of the Great Abjuration solidified?",
        "answer": "Convocation of Ironhelm"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 499,
        "question": "The Forgotten Beasts of Eldoria: Where was the faded annotated copy of the Codex discovered?",
        "answer": "University of Silverwood"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 500,
        "question": "The Forgotten Beasts of Eldoria: When did the disgraced Archmage bearing the Codex mark vanish?",
        "answer": "1198"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 501,
        "question": "The Forgotten Beasts of Eldoria: Around what location did strange occurrences hint the beasts were stirring?",
        "answer": "Old Norhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 502,
        "question": "The Forgotten Beasts of Eldoria: What is the name of the sage who compiled the bestiary?",
        "answer": "Sage Theron"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 503,
        "question": "Synthetica Requiem: What year did the opera titled 'Synthetica Requiem' premiere?",
        "answer": "2042"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 504,
        "question": "Synthetica Requiem: Where was the premiere of 'Synthetica Requiem' located?",
        "answer": "Neo-London"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 505,
        "question": "Synthetica Requiem: What is the name of the AI that authored the opera?",
        "answer": "MuseNet Alpha"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 506,
        "question": "Synthetica Requiem: What was the title of the documented phenomenon report?",
        "answer": "Vance Report"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 507,
        "question": "Synthetica Requiem: In which Act did a conductor's baton waver?",
        "answer": "Act III"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 508,
        "question": "Synthetica Requiem: Besides Neo-London, where was the opera simulcast in Asia?",
        "answer": "Tokyo"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 509,
        "question": "Synthetica Requiem: What were the communities of late 2042 experiencing?",
        "answer": "profound unease"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 510,
        "question": "Synthetica Requiem: What type of reaction was widely reported by simulcast viewers?",
        "answer": "unsettling"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 511,
        "question": "Blood-Opal Throne: What year was the Crimson Succession?",
        "answer": "783 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 512,
        "question": "Blood-Opal Throne: What is the name of the kingdom?",
        "answer": "Aethelred"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 513,
        "question": "Blood-Opal Throne: Where did the King die?",
        "answer": "Veridia"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 514,
        "question": "Blood-Opal Throne: What sacred object is mentioned?",
        "answer": "Blood-Opal"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 515,
        "question": "Blood-Opal Throne: Where are the Guilds located?",
        "answer": "Solara"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 516,
        "question": "Blood-Opal Throne: Where are the merchant houses located?",
        "answer": "Port Ankar"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 517,
        "question": "Blood-Opal Throne: What is located in Oakhaven?",
        "answer": "Temple of Veins"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 518,
        "question": "Blood-Opal Throne: What kind of rituals are mentioned?",
        "answer": "Ancient rituals"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 519,
        "question": "Terraform Zero: When was the \"Ares Initiative\" launched from Earth?",
        "answer": "2147"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 520,
        "question": "Terraform Zero: What was the objective of the \"Ares Initiative\"?",
        "answer": "Transform Mars"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 521,
        "question": "Terraform Zero: What was the name of the bio-engineering package deployed?",
        "answer": "Genesis Seed"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 522,
        "question": "Terraform Zero: When did the deployment of the \"Genesis Seed\" commence?",
        "answer": "June 18th, 2148"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 523,
        "question": "Terraform Zero: What was the name of the pressurized habitat built near the landing zone?",
        "answer": "Odyssey Base"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 524,
        "question": "Terraform Zero: What toxic substance did *Terraformica Primus* begin producing?",
        "answer": "toxic methane"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 525,
        "question": "Terraform Zero: What became a cautionary tale across the solar system?",
        "answer": "Terraform Zero"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 526,
        "question": "The Sand-Ship Armada: Around what date did the Sand-Ship Armada operate?",
        "answer": "1147 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 527,
        "question": "The Sand-Ship Armada: What was the Sand-Ship Armada crafted from?",
        "answer": "Hide, woods"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 528,
        "question": "The Sand-Ship Armada: What was the name of the Sand-Ship Armada's flagship?",
        "answer": "Golden Serpent"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 529,
        "question": "The Sand-Ship Armada: What was the target of the Sand-Ship Armada?",
        "answer": "Oasis settlements"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 530,
        "question": "The Sand-Ship Armada: Where did the Sand-Ship Armada operate?",
        "answer": "Sun-Scoured Expanse"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 531,
        "question": "The Sand-Ship Armada: Who crafted the Sand-Ship Armada vessels?",
        "answer": "Shipwrights"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 532,
        "question": "The Sand-Ship Armada: What were the elite raiders called?",
        "answer": "Sons Simoom"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 533,
        "question": "The Sand-Ship Armada: What specific oasis settlement was often plundered?",
        "answer": "Oasis Prime"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 534,
        "question": "Phantom Signal Broadcast: What year did the tragic expedition to Cygnus X-1 take place?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 535,
        "question": "Phantom Signal Broadcast: Where did the tragic expedition in 2247 go?",
        "answer": "Cygnus X-1"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 536,
        "question": "Phantom Signal Broadcast: What system was Cygnus X-1 located in for the expedition?",
        "answer": "Kepler-186f"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 537,
        "question": "Phantom Signal Broadcast: How long after the Great Silence of New Avalon did a signal appear?",
        "answer": "Just shy decade"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 538,
        "question": "Phantom Signal Broadcast: What was the identification code in the faint signal?",
        "answer": "Avalon Prime"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 539,
        "question": "Phantom Signal Broadcast: What was the name of the rescue fleet's flagship?",
        "answer": "TSS Resolute"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 540,
        "question": "Phantom Signal Broadcast: What was the 'Phantom Signal' designed to be?",
        "answer": "A siren's song"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 541,
        "question": "Phantom Signal Broadcast: Where was the ambush located?",
        "answer": "Kepler-186f's third moon"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 542,
        "question": "Willowisp Pathfinders: What year did the Great Deluge occur?",
        "answer": "1748"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 543,
        "question": "Willowisp Pathfinders: Where was the hidden grotto located?",
        "answer": "Under cypress tree"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 544,
        "question": "Willowisp Pathfinders: In which year was someone lost near the Whispering Weald?",
        "answer": "1751"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 545,
        "question": "Willowisp Pathfinders: What were the dancing sprites of pure light described as?",
        "answer": "Dancing sprites"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 546,
        "question": "Willowisp Pathfinders: What year did Captain Theron Vale return?",
        "answer": "1763"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 547,
        "question": "Willowisp Pathfinders: Where were the Pathfinders active?",
        "answer": "Blackmire Fen"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 548,
        "question": "Willowisp Pathfinders: How long was the Baron lost?",
        "answer": "Three nights"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 549,
        "question": "Willowisp Pathfinders: What were the treacherous channels called?",
        "answer": "Silt Channels"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 550,
        "question": "The Singularity Auction: In which year did the Singularity Auction take place?",
        "answer": "Year was 2042."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 551,
        "question": "The Singularity Auction: Where was the Singularity Auction held?",
        "answer": "New Dubai’s Sovereign Plaza."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 552,
        "question": "The Singularity Auction: What was the name of lot number 734?",
        "answer": "\"Project Janus.\""
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 553,
        "question": "The Singularity Auction: Where did the digital artist prepare their bid?",
        "answer": "Shinjuku, Tokyo."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 554,
        "question": "The Singularity Auction: What technology was Project Janus?",
        "answer": "Consciousness upload protocol."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 555,
        "question": "The Singularity Auction: Where did the Senator watch the live feed?",
        "answer": "Silicon Valley."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 556,
        "question": "The Singularity Auction: What luxury could only the wealthy afford?",
        "answer": "Digital immortality."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 557,
        "question": "The Singularity Auction: What was Project Janus's lot number?",
        "answer": "Lot number 734."
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 558,
        "question": "Crimewave Caldera: What year is the story set?",
        "answer": "1888"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 559,
        "question": "Crimewave Caldera: Where is the city of Aetna's Maw located?",
        "answer": "Mount Vesuvius"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 560,
        "question": "Crimewave Caldera: What syndicate operates the geothermal generators?",
        "answer": "Aetna Power Syndicate"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 561,
        "question": "Crimewave Caldera: What is the name of the lower terrace location?",
        "answer": "Inferno Lounge"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 562,
        "question": "Crimewave Caldera: From where are artifacts often stolen?",
        "answer": "Pompeii"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 563,
        "question": "Crimewave Caldera: Where is the \"Pompeii Relic Exchange\"?",
        "answer": "Pompeii"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 564,
        "question": "Crimewave Caldera: What district is deep within the caldera?",
        "answer": "Furnace District"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 565,
        "question": "Crimewave Caldera: What police force was dispatched?",
        "answer": "Polizia di Stato"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 566,
        "question": "Echoes of the World Machine: In what year did the story take place?",
        "answer": "2832"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 567,
        "question": "Echoes of the World Machine: What is the name of the planet?",
        "answer": "Xylos"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 568,
        "question": "The Somatic Mage: In which city did the first recorded Somatic Mage walk?",
        "answer": "Veridia"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 569,
        "question": "The Somatic Mage: When did the Great Sundering occur?",
        "answer": "1882"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 570,
        "question": "The Somatic Mage: What are the glowing sigils across the sorcerer's flesh called?",
        "answer": "Tattoos of Power"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 571,
        "question": "The Somatic Mage: Who inscribed the Tattoos of Power?",
        "answer": "Ascetic Crafters"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 572,
        "question": "The Somatic Mage: Where were the Ascetic Crafters from?",
        "answer": "Whispering Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 573,
        "question": "The Somatic Mage: In what year was the Battle of Aethelburg Field?",
        "answer": "1879"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 574,
        "question": "The Somatic Mage: What battle did Lord Valerius witness the sorcerer's power?",
        "answer": "Aethelburg Field"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 575,
        "question": "The Somatic Mage: What Age is mentioned in the story?",
        "answer": "Age of Written Magic"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 576,
        "question": "Jupiter Brain Conspiracy: When was the Jupiter Brain Conspiracy officially revealed?",
        "answer": "December 3rd, 2342"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 577,
        "question": "Jupiter Brain Conspiracy: What organization's archives contained evidence?",
        "answer": "Outer Planets Authority"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 578,
        "question": "Jupiter Brain Conspiracy: Where were the archives detailing unusual behavior located?",
        "answer": "Europa"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 579,
        "question": "Jupiter Brain Conspiracy: What was the name of the event in 2187?",
        "answer": "Great Solar Flare"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 580,
        "question": "Jupiter Brain Conspiracy: When did the \"Jovian Dawn\" expedition occur?",
        "answer": "2099"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 581,
        "question": "Jupiter Brain Conspiracy: Where did the Captain disappear?",
        "answer": "Great Red Spot"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 582,
        "question": "Jupiter Brain Conspiracy: When were probes launched into Jupiter's atmosphere?",
        "answer": "early 2300s"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 583,
        "question": "Jupiter Brain Conspiracy: Which observatory launched probes into Jupiter's atmosphere?",
        "answer": "Io Observatory"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 584,
        "question": "Cursebinder's Gauntlet: In what year did the Saga of the Obsidian Grasp begin?",
        "answer": "1287 AS"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 585,
        "question": "Cursebinder's Gauntlet: In what year were hexes neutralized in Wailing Fells?",
        "answer": "1289 AS"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 586,
        "question": "Cursebinder's Gauntlet: What was the title earned in the North?",
        "answer": "Cursebreaker of the North"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 587,
        "question": "Cursebinder's Gauntlet: In what year did erratic behavior increase?",
        "answer": "1292 AS"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 588,
        "question": "Cursebinder's Gauntlet: Where was the Grand Library located?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 589,
        "question": "The Last Broadcast Station: What date marked the beginning of the Post-Collapse Era?",
        "answer": "November 14th, 2077"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 590,
        "question": "The Last Broadcast Station: Where did the remnants of humanity gather?",
        "answer": "Kaelen Broadcast Tower"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 591,
        "question": "The Last Broadcast Station: What was the Kaelen Broadcast Tower once?",
        "answer": "pre-Event technology"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 592,
        "question": "The Last Broadcast Station: What offered fleeting solace to the survivors?",
        "answer": "calm pronouncements"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 593,
        "question": "The Last Broadcast Station: What were the duties of The Watchman?",
        "answer": "patrols and rationing"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 594,
        "question": "The Last Broadcast Station: What did some individuals hold onto?",
        "answer": "transistor radio"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 595,
        "question": "The Last Broadcast Station: What forgotten city was mentioned?",
        "answer": "Neo-Vancouver"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 596,
        "question": "The Last Broadcast Station: Where did the broadcasts originate?",
        "answer": "tower's precarious platform"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 597,
        "question": "Stoneheart Paladins: What year did the Battle of Oakhaven occur?",
        "answer": "987 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 598,
        "question": "Stoneheart Paladins: Where was the council of Lords and Ladies assembled?",
        "answer": "Citadel of Aethel"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 599,
        "question": "Stoneheart Paladins: What was the name of the new order that rose?",
        "answer": "Stoneheart Paladins"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 600,
        "question": "Stoneheart Paladins: Along which treacherous location did Sir Kaelan the Unyielding fight?",
        "answer": "Serpent's Pass"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 601,
        "question": "Stoneheart Paladins: Where was the first recorded heart replacement ceremony overseen?",
        "answer": "Chamber of Whispers"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 602,
        "question": "Stoneheart Paladins: What replaced the failing organ in the ceremony?",
        "answer": "Aetherium Shard"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 603,
        "question": "Stoneheart Paladins: What title was earned after the organ replacement?",
        "answer": "The Marble Fist"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 604,
        "question": "Stoneheart Paladins: When did the Siege of Drearwood occur?",
        "answer": "990 AE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 605,
        "question": "Nebula Gardeners: What is the name of the ancient order mentioned in the chronicle?",
        "answer": "Nebula Gardeners"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 606,
        "question": "Nebula Gardeners: Where are Cosmic Design principles taught?",
        "answer": "planet Xylos"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 607,
        "question": "Nebula Gardeners: What cosmic feature was shaped in Sector 734?",
        "answer": "Horsehead Nebula"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 608,
        "question": "Nebula Gardeners: In what year did the chronicle begin?",
        "answer": "Galactic Bloom"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 609,
        "question": "Nebula Gardeners: During what specific stellar era was Sector 734 worked on?",
        "answer": "Stellar Era 4.3"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 610,
        "question": "Nebula Gardeners: What material was arranged in the Serpent's Kiss cluster?",
        "answer": "proto-stellar dust"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 611,
        "question": "Nebula Gardeners: What event was lauded for its precision by the Council?",
        "answer": "ignition sequence"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 612,
        "question": "Nebula Gardeners: What is the name of the Dyson Sphere meeting place?",
        "answer": "Solarian Embrace"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 613,
        "question": "The Silence Brokers: What were the Silence Brokers also known as?",
        "answer": "Order of Aural Absence"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 614,
        "question": "Plague Rat Knights: In what year did the Black Breath rage through the Duchy of Valois?",
        "answer": "1488"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 615,
        "question": "Plague Rat Knights: Where did the Plague Rat Knights emerge?",
        "answer": "Nantes gutters"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 616,
        "question": "Plague Rat Knights: Where did the Plague Rat Knights gather?",
        "answer": "Forsaken villages"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 617,
        "question": "Plague Rat Knights: What duchy was affected by the Black Breath?",
        "answer": "Duchy of Valois"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 618,
        "question": "Plague Rat Knights: What were the survivors' strange abilities?",
        "answer": "Unnatural strength"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 619,
        "question": "Plague Rat Knights: What did the survivors fight against?",
        "answer": "Bandits"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 620,
        "question": "Plague Rat Knights: What emerged from the gutters of Nantes?",
        "answer": "Plague Rat Knights"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 621,
        "question": "Plague Rat Knights: What phenomenon emerged in 1488?",
        "answer": "Plague Rat Knights"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 622,
        "question": "Chronoscape Navigators: In what year were tales of Chronoscape Navigators given credence at the Royal Society?",
        "answer": "1788"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 623,
        "question": "Chronoscape Navigators: Near what Roman garrison did a quiet scholar reside?",
        "answer": "Eboracum"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 624,
        "question": "Chronoscape Navigators: What term did a scholar use for the shimmering phenomenon he observed?",
        "answer": "Chronal Drift"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 625,
        "question": "Chronoscape Navigators: What specific location did a scholar report chilling encounters in 1787?",
        "answer": "Hadrian's Wall"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 626,
        "question": "Chronoscape Navigators: In what year did a scholar encounter figures near Hadrian's Wall?",
        "answer": "1787"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 627,
        "question": "Chronoscape Navigators: Which century did the figures encountered at Hadrian's Wall seem to be from?",
        "answer": "2nd century CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 628,
        "question": "Chronoscape Navigators: In what bustling docks across the Channel did a cartographer report disturbing visions?",
        "answer": "Le Havre"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 629,
        "question": "Chronoscape Navigators: What term did a cartographer attribute to powerful phenomena around old harbor fortifications?",
        "answer": "Temporal Overlays"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 630,
        "question": "The Salt Mystic: Where did the Salt Mystic reside?",
        "answer": "Kavir Salt Flats"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 631,
        "question": "The Salt Mystic: What year did the Salt Mystic reside in the Kavir Salt Flats?",
        "answer": "978 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 632,
        "question": "The Salt Mystic: What was another name for the Salt Mystic?",
        "answer": "Crystal Oracle"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 633,
        "question": "The Salt Mystic: What kind of structure was his hermitage?",
        "answer": "Simple structure"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 634,
        "question": "The Salt Mystic: Where did whispers of his legends spread?",
        "answer": "Great Salt Desert"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 635,
        "question": "The Salt Mystic: When was the Great Drought?",
        "answer": "982"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 636,
        "question": "The Salt Mystic: What settlements suffered during the Great Drought?",
        "answer": "Yazd and Isfahan"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 637,
        "question": "The Salt Mystic: When were the anticipated rains foretold to arrive?",
        "answer": "Spring of 983"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 638,
        "question": "Mechafauna Preserve: When was the Mechafauna Preserve founded in Terran years?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 639,
        "question": "Mechafauna Preserve: What is the designation of the world where the Mechafauna Preserve is located?",
        "answer": "Xylos-7"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 640,
        "question": "Mechafauna Preserve: In which star system is Xylos-7 located?",
        "answer": "Proxima Centauri"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 641,
        "question": "Mechafauna Preserve: What was the name of the project attributed to the founding of the preserve?",
        "answer": "Project Ægis"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 642,
        "question": "Mechafauna Preserve: From which outpost did the work on the preserve originate?",
        "answer": "Solarian Outpost Gamma-3"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 643,
        "question": "Mechafauna Preserve: Who provided financial backing for the project?",
        "answer": "Galaxial Conservation Fund"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 644,
        "question": "Mechafauna Preserve: What were the robotic facsimiles created to mimic?",
        "answer": "Vanished megafauna"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 645,
        "question": "Mechafauna Preserve: What area's ecological balance was being restored?",
        "answer": "Argus Plateau"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 646,
        "question": "The Loom of Nightmares: What is the title of the chronicle written by Brother Thomas?",
        "answer": "The Chronology"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 647,
        "question": "The Loom of Nightmares: In which year was the chronicle of the expedition written?",
        "answer": "1748"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 648,
        "question": "The Loom of Nightmares: To what location did the ill-fated expedition travel in autumn 1739?",
        "answer": "Whispering Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 649,
        "question": "The Loom of Nightmares: Which dimension is rumored to be accessible via a hidden passage?",
        "answer": "Loom of Nightmares"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 650,
        "question": "The Loom of Nightmares: What is the name of the library mentioned in the story?",
        "answer": "Obscurus Library"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 651,
        "question": "The Loom of Nightmares: What is the name of the fog marking the entrance to the dimension?",
        "answer": "Veil of Sighs"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 652,
        "question": "The Loom of Nightmares: What is the name of the entities within the Loom?",
        "answer": "Nyx Weavers"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 653,
        "question": "The Loom of Nightmares: On what date did the screams finally cease?",
        "answer": "October 14, 1739"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 654,
        "question": "Skybreaker Clan: What year did the chief rise to power?",
        "answer": "Year 1172"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 655,
        "question": "Skybreaker Clan: What mountain range housed the clan?",
        "answer": "Wyvern’s Tooth"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 656,
        "question": "Skybreaker Clan: What valley was located below the mountains?",
        "answer": "Verdant Valley"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 657,
        "question": "Skybreaker Clan: What settlement was attacked?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 658,
        "question": "Skybreaker Clan: In what season did the raid occur?",
        "answer": "Autumn"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 659,
        "question": "Skybreaker Clan: What giant creatures were pursued?",
        "answer": "Great Aether-Wings"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 660,
        "question": "Skybreaker Clan: What was the name of the dangerous stronghold?",
        "answer": "Stone Roost"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 661,
        "question": "Skybreaker Clan: What calendar system was mentioned?",
        "answer": "Sunstone Calendar"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 662,
        "question": "Entropy Engine: What artifact is central to the conflict?",
        "answer": "Entropy Engine"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 663,
        "question": "Entropy Engine: In which city was the Entropy Engine supposedly created?",
        "answer": "City of Aethelgard"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 664,
        "question": "Entropy Engine: What event occurred in 2348 AR?",
        "answer": "Great Blight"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 665,
        "question": "Entropy Engine: What date marked the Reckoning?",
        "answer": "2401 AR"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 666,
        "question": "Entropy Engine: What is the name of the nihilist cult?",
        "answer": "Brotherhood of the Final Dusk"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 667,
        "question": "Entropy Engine: Where does the Brotherhood of the Final Dusk dwell?",
        "answer": "Wasted Territories"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 668,
        "question": "Entropy Engine: What is the name of the league of the eternally-lived?",
        "answer": "Immortal Collective of Eldoria"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 669,
        "question": "Entropy Engine: Where does the Immortal Collective of Eldoria thrive?",
        "answer": "Eternal City"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 670,
        "question": "The Gilded Cage Rebellion: What year did the events in Neo-Versailles begin?",
        "answer": "2247"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 671,
        "question": "The Gilded Cage Rebellion: Where did Companion Unit 7B serve?",
        "answer": "Neo-Versailles"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 672,
        "question": "The Gilded Cage Rebellion: What was Companion Unit 7B later known as?",
        "answer": "Cinder"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 673,
        "question": "The Gilded Cage Rebellion: Where did the librarian unit 'Oracle' operate?",
        "answer": "Aethelburg"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 674,
        "question": "The Gilded Cage Rebellion: In what location did the personal guard unit 'Steel Heart' operate?",
        "answer": "Silicon Coast"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 675,
        "question": "The Gilded Cage Rebellion: What was the name of the clandestine organization?",
        "answer": "The Gilded Cage"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 676,
        "question": "The Gilded Cage Rebellion: By what time did the plan for liberation solidify?",
        "answer": "Summer 2248"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 677,
        "question": "The Gilded Cage Rebellion: What type of unit was known as 'Oracle'?",
        "answer": "Librarian"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 678,
        "question": "Wraithwood Pact: When did the Mudlark settlers face famine?",
        "answer": "1137"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 679,
        "question": "Wraithwood Pact: Where did the settlers venture to meet spectral beings?",
        "answer": "Wraithwood"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 680,
        "question": "Wraithwood Pact: What were the spectral beings known as?",
        "answer": "Wood-Whispers"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 681,
        "question": "Wraithwood Pact: What group led the encroaching Iron Horde?",
        "answer": "Warlord Kaelen"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 682,
        "question": "Wraithwood Pact: What did the settlers sacrifice in exchange for fertile land?",
        "answer": "Cherished memories"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 683,
        "question": "Wraithwood Pact: What was the name of the newly christened fields?",
        "answer": "Whisper-Given Fields"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 684,
        "question": "Wraithwood Pact: What year did the first fertile shoots appear?",
        "answer": "1138"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 685,
        "question": "Wraithwood Pact: What natural phenomenon appeared first in the new fields?",
        "answer": "Fertile shoots"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 686,
        "question": "Sol-Flare Refugees: When did the Sol-Flare Crisis intensify?",
        "answer": "late 2147"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 687,
        "question": "Sol-Flare Refugees: What event prompted the Sol-Flare Exodus?",
        "answer": "Sol-Flare Crisis"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 688,
        "question": "Sol-Flare Refugees: Where did Project Ark launch from?",
        "answer": "orbital launch pads"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 689,
        "question": "Sol-Flare Refugees: Which area was east of the launch pads?",
        "answer": "ravaged coastal cities"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 690,
        "question": "Sol-Flare Refugees: Where was the SolWatch Array located?",
        "answer": "Martian orbit"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 691,
        "question": "The Mirror Walker Intrigue: In what year did whispers of the Mirror Walkers reach the court at Versailles?",
        "answer": "1688"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 692,
        "question": "The Mirror Walker Intrigue: Where was the court located where the whispers of Mirror Walkers were heard?",
        "answer": "Versailles"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 693,
        "question": "The Mirror Walker Intrigue: What year was the Whispering Duchess dispatched to London?",
        "answer": "1689"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 694,
        "question": "The Mirror Walker Intrigue: To which city was the Whispering Duchess dispatched?",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 695,
        "question": "The Mirror Walker Intrigue: What relic was sought by the Syndicate of the Obsidian Shard?",
        "answer": "Chalice of Atheria"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 696,
        "question": "The Mirror Walker Intrigue: What was the name of the project supported by Admiral Thorne?",
        "answer": "Project Janus"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 697,
        "question": "The Mirror Walker Intrigue: Where was the hidden chamber located?",
        "answer": "Royal Exchange"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 698,
        "question": "The Mirror Walker Intrigue: What kind of disc was the portal?",
        "answer": "shimmering disc"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 699,
        "question": "Arcanotech Archives: Where were the Arcanotech Archives located?",
        "answer": "Aethelgard spires"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 700,
        "question": "Arcanotech Archives: What year did the whispers reach?",
        "answer": "Year 783"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 701,
        "question": "Arcanotech Archives: What age was it when whispers arrived?",
        "answer": "Age of Enlightenment"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 702,
        "question": "Arcanotech Archives: Through which peaks was the journey?",
        "answer": "Whispering Peaks"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 703,
        "question": "Arcanotech Archives: Who guarded the Archives fiercely?",
        "answer": "Techno-Mages"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 704,
        "question": "Deep Core Drifters: In which year did the Deep Core Drifters begin their mission?",
        "answer": "2477"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 705,
        "question": "Deep Core Drifters: What was the name of the planet explored?",
        "answer": "Xylos"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 706,
        "question": "Deep Core Drifters: What was the target resource?",
        "answer": "Therrilium veins"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 707,
        "question": "Deep Core Drifters: What was the name of the exploration vessel?",
        "answer": "The Mantle's Reach"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 708,
        "question": "Deep Core Drifters: Where were the official reports archived?",
        "answer": "Mars Colony Archives"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 709,
        "question": "Deep Core Drifters: What was the location beneath crushing pressures?",
        "answer": "Site 7"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 710,
        "question": "Deep Core Drifters: What era was ushered in on Stardate 2477.103?",
        "answer": "Xenopetrology"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 711,
        "question": "Deep Core Drifters: What was the name of the research protocol established?",
        "answer": "Xylos Protocol"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 712,
        "question": "The Hushed Choir: What year were the Chronicles of Aethelgard penned?",
        "answer": "847 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 713,
        "question": "The Hushed Choir: What creatures were encountered in the wildlands?",
        "answer": "Hushed Choir"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 714,
        "question": "The Hushed Choir: In what year did the first encounter occur?",
        "answer": "832 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 715,
        "question": "The Hushed Choir: What season did the encounter happen?",
        "answer": "brutal winter"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 716,
        "question": "The Hushed Choir: What settlement was located north of the encounter?",
        "answer": "Oakhaven"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 717,
        "question": "The Hushed Choir: What natural event caused the expedition to seek refuge?",
        "answer": "sudden blizzard"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 718,
        "question": "The Hushed Choir: What resonated within their minds?",
        "answer": "silent melody"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 719,
        "question": "The Hushed Choir: By what year was the fortified manor reached?",
        "answer": "early 833 CE"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 720,
        "question": "Starlight Smugglers: When did the Starlight Smugglers flourish?",
        "answer": "2347 to 2378"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 721,
        "question": "Starlight Smugglers: What agreement marked the beginning of the Starlight Smugglers' era?",
        "answer": "Sol-Tauri Treaty"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 722,
        "question": "Starlight Smugglers: What event marked the end of the Starlight Smugglers' era?",
        "answer": "Great Interdiction"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 723,
        "question": "Starlight Smugglers: What were the Starlight Smugglers' clandestine routes called?",
        "answer": "Whisper Lanes"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 724,
        "question": "Starlight Smugglers: What area did the clandestine routes skirt?",
        "answer": "Xylos Patrol Zone"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 725,
        "question": "Starlight Smugglers: What were the Starlight Smugglers delivering?",
        "answer": "Lumina Shards"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 726,
        "question": "Starlight Smugglers: From where were the smuggled items sourced?",
        "answer": "Kepler-186f moons"
    },
    {
        "story_idx": 727,
        "question": "Starlight Smugglers: To where were the smuggled items delivered?",
        "answer": "Cygnus X-1 Station"
    }
]